(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)Enjoy yourself.
You're gonna be in the presence of
something I've dreamed of for decades.
I hope you'll appreciate...
(Sheldon:)...the magnitude of where you are,
and what it represents.
(Penny:)I'll talk to Leonard.
(Sheldon:)-You will?
-Yes.
(Penny:)If it means that much to you,
you should go.
(Sheldon(Hugging her):)Oh, Penny, thank you.
(Penny:)-You're welcome.
-Since I rarely hug...
(Sheldon:)...I'm relying on your expertise
regarding duration.
(Penny:)-I think we're there.
-Oh, good.
(Howard(on the phone):)Bye-bye.
(Raj:)Even though I don't have a girlfriend, I
can still have a good time on Valentine's.
(Howard:)Trust me, you can't. I've tried.
(Raj:)No, no, no.
I'm gonna have a "me" day.
I'm gonna go
to one of those spas in Koreatown...
...take a steam, get a massage.